fantomaster.com 2012-04-12

# About fantomaster.com: who we are - our privacy policy - 2012-04-12

## Our Mission

Our mission statement at **fantomaster.com** can be summarized in five straightforward words:

### Exceptional products — quality beats quantity!

The past decade's technological development has inundated the world with software and computer related services, including truly excellent ones. Thousands of corporations and individual brains make a daily point of developing the most sophisticated solutions. And even if — as anywhere in life — not all may actually be what it seems, overall users' standards and expectations have sharpened and qualified themselves in the course of recent years.

User value is the call of the day. Fair service is gaining steadily in importance — and the more people are becoming aware of the innate possibilities and limits of information technology, the greater the demand for specialized solutions: software which stands out amongst the mass market standard fare, which does what is promised and which, for a change, actually helps resolve more problems than it creates.

## phantomLine™ Software and Service Features

ISPs, webmasters, WWW designers, layouters, graphics artists, advertising and promotion agencies, search engine positioning facilitators, web copy writers and programmers— our software and services will help you survive the Internet and the current e-commerce revolution by offering the following features:

  * enhancing your Internet presence by supporting your **positioning and ranking efforts** in all major and minor **search engines**
  * first time ever **automatic generation of keyword density** optimised phantom or cloaking pages in unprecedented precision
  * state of the art software and solutions to guard your site effectively against **code napping** and **spamming** by unethical competitors
  * **position analysis** tools to aid you in your search engine registration efforts
  * world's most comprehensive database of verified **search engine spiders (crawlers)**
  * **web site administration** tools for easy **string conversion** , sophisticated **log file evaluation** and enhanced server based **file handling**
  * a wide variety of **practice based tools** to help you facilitate your everyday activities as a webmaster and system administrator, saving you time and money
  * high caliber **professional consultation** for web based businesses focusing on search engine position optimization and efficient web marketing

See our Terms of Service here!

## About fantomaster

**fantomaster.com** is a registered private limited liability company based in Belgium (Europe).

Corporate Data

Online since 1999-11-01

fantomaster.com GmbH
    Postfach 19
    B-4760 Büllingen
    EU VAT ID/T.V.A.: BE 0463.684.942
     
Marketing & Sales & Support Dept.
CEO & CMO
Ralph Tegtmeier M.A.
    Phone: +32-80-549.247
    Fax: +32-80-549.248
    U.S. #: (650) 557-2088
    UK   #:  020-3239-5569 – New!
    ANZ #:  (02) 8003 4253
    Skype: [**fantomaster_ralph**](callto:fantomaster_ralph)
    E-Mail: 

Technology & Development Dept.
CEO & CTO
Dr. rer. nat. Dirk Brockhausen
    Phone: +49-6557-901.857
    Fax: +49-6557-901.858
    U.S. #: (650) 557-2104
    UK   #:  020-3239-8622 – New!
    ANZ #:  (02) 8003 4095
    Skype: [ **fantomaster_dirk**](callto:fantomaster_dirk)
    E-Mail: 

The web site domain and the related _fantomas phantomLine™_ software and services are the protected trade marks and intellectual property of _fantomaster.com_. Our staff consists of highly experienced IT technicians, programmers, support and marketing experts well conversant with the Internet in general and the WWW in particular.

## Privacy Statement

### Declaration of Intent

**fantomaster.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: http://www.fantomaster.com.

#### IP addresses

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address may be used to gather broad demographic information.

#### Email addresses

Email addresses gathered from your subscription to our newsletter(s) will never be rented out or sold for marketing or other purposes. Neither will they be divulged without your express permission unless stipulated by legally binding court order.

#### Cookies

This site may use cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.

This site may contain links to other sites. **fantomaster.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we may use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

#### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

#### Children's Guidelines

This web site meets the guidelines of [TRUSTe's](http://www.truste.org/) Children's program.

  * We do **NOT** collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent.
  * We do **NOT** collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent.
  * We do **NOT** distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information without prior parental consent.
  * We do **NOT** give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent.
  * We do **NOT** entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact:

fantomaster.com GmbH
    Postfach 19
    B-4760 Büllingen
    Belgium
    Phone: +32-80-549.247
    Fax: +32-80-549.248

U.S. and Canadian clients

(When calling from the USA or Canada, please substitute _“011”_ for _“+”_ in the numbers above!)  
Or, call our U.S. numbers directly:  
– (650) 557-2088 (Sales + Marketing)  
– (650) 557-2104 (Tech Support + Development)

UK clients

Clients in the UK can also call us directly on our new UK numbers:  
– 020-3239-5569 (Sales + Marketing)  
– 020-3239-8622 (Tech Support + Development)

Australian and New Zealander clients

Clients in Australia and New Zealand can also call us directly on our ANZ numbers:  
– (02) 8003 4253 (Sales + Marketing)  
– (02) 8003 4095 (Tech Support + Development)

## Office Hours

Your time zone: 3:00 PM  4:00 AM 

Our time zone: 4:00 PM 5:00 AM

Office Hours: From» To»

Currently, our time is: 1:33 AM  while your time is: 0:33 AM 

And in case you're wondering: yes, we have adjusted our working hours to better accommodate our US and Canadian clients.

Script courtesy of <http://willmaster.com/>

## Awards

The Spider Award

Ranked #1 in Category   
“Top 10 Position”  
[June 2000]

This award was issued by the (immensely recommendable) Spider-Food site over at: <http://spider-food.net/>

Note that this is none of the usual convenience awards so abundant on the web.

To qualify, you had to prove a Top10 ranking with AltaVista — no tricks like cloaking, doorways, etc., allowed, either!

There was an additional bonus for a #1 ranking (which we received as well for the keyword phrase — did you guess? — “cloaking technology”)
